Introduction
Chapter 1 The Critical Importance of Leadership Transitions
Chapter 2 Diagnosing the Situation and Understanding the Context
Chapter 3 Accelerating Learning and Building Foundational Knowledge
Chapter 4 Securing Early Wins and Establishing Credibility
Chapter 5 Building Relationships and Creating Alliances
Chapter 6 Aligning Strategy, Structure, and Team
Chapter 7 Adapting Leadership Style to the Situation
Chapter 8 Avoiding Common Traps and Pitfalls
Chapter 9 Creating Systems for Ongoing Growth and Feedback
Chapter 10 Sustaining Momentum and Leading for the Long Term
Conclusion